dragonnest.eu 2019-07-23

# Dragon Nest Europe: Free-to-Play Online Action RPG

At Cherry Credits, we value the importance of your privacy by complying with applicable laws for the protection of your privacy, including, without limitation, the Singapore Personal Data Protection Act (“PDPA”) and European Union General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR"). Our Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be received or collected when registering with Cherry Credits or using any of our services and also some of the measures we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

By accessing our websites and / or using the materials, facilities and / or services offered through our websites, you agree that, Singapore law (including without Limitation, the provisions of the Evidence Act (Cap. 97), the Electronic Transactions Act (Cap. 88) and the Personal Data Protection Act (PDPA)) shall govern such access and the provision of such materials, facilities and/or services and you agree to submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the Singapore courts.

Upon submission of your personal identifiable information on or through this website, you are giving us your consent to collect, use and disclose your personal identifiable information in the manner as set forth in our Privacy Policy.

### 1\. Why we collect personal information?

Your personal data is collected when you register a Cherry account with us for the following reasons.

  * where it is necessary for the performance of our agreement with you to provide a full-featured payment and gaming services and deliver associated Content and Services;
  * where it is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate and legal interests of Cherry Credits or a third party (e.g. the interests of our other customers), except where such interests are overridden by your prevailing legitimate interests and rights; or
  * where you have given consent to it.

Some of these information is essential for us to verify your identity should there be a need for any form of identity verification. Your personal information helps us to keep you informed on our latest announcements, updates, and events. If you do not want us to keep you up-to-date with our latest news and services, you may edit your preferences in your Cherry account.

### 2\. Your Cherry account and related information

Cherry Credits allows you to create a Cherry account using your personal information. This registration allows you to access our products and services. Should you need to make a purchase transaction, all you need is to login your Cherry account.

### 3\. What information we collect and how we may use it?

3.1 Basic Account Data

Your email address and IP address are collected when you register with us. With your email address as the login ID, you are required to choose a password as your login credentials. The provision of this information is necessary to register a Cherry account.

3.2 Full Account Data

Your personal information, including your full name, date of birth, identification number, country of residence are required when you upgrade your basic account to a full account. To safeguard your account, these essential information allow us to verify that you are the genuine owner of a specific Cherry account. We may at times, need to share your information in order to provide the product or service you have requested.

3.3 Transaction and Payment Data

In order to make a transaction on Cherry Credits (e.g. to fund your e-wallet, or to purchase Content and/or Services), you need to provide payment information to Cherry Credits to facilitate the transaction. If you choose to pay using credit card, you need to provide us your credit card information (name, address), which we will process and transmit to the payment service provider of your choice to enable the transaction including performing of anti-fraud checks. Likewise, Cherry Credits will receive data from your payment service provider for the same reasons.

3.4 Other Data You Explicitly Submit

We will collect and process Personal Data whenever you explicitly provide it to us or send it as part of communication on any Cherry platform. E.g. Cherry Forums, Cherry Messenger, or when you provide feedback or other user generated content. This data includes: 

  * Information that you post, comment or follow in any of our Content and Services;
  * Information you provide when you request information or support from us or purchase Content and Services from us, including information necessary to process your orders with the relevant payment merchant or, in case of physical goods, shipping providers;
  * Information you provide to us when participating in competitions, contests and tournaments or responding to surveys, e.g. your contact details.

We may also use such information during our auditing, research, and analysis process to improve our products and services. 

3.5 Your Use of Cherry Game Clients and Websites

We collect a variety of information through your general interaction with the websites, Content and Services offered by Cherry Credits. Personal Data we collect may include, but is not limited to, browser and device information, data collected through automated electronic interactions and application usage data. Likewise, we will track your process across our websites and applications to verify that you are not a bot and to optimize our services.

In order to provide you with services, we need to collect, store and use various information about your activity in our Content and Services. "Content-Related Information" includes your Cherry account ID, as well as what is usually referred to as "game statistics". By game statistics, we mean information about your games' preferences, progress in the games, playtime, as well as information about the device you are using, including what operating system you are using, device settings, unique device identifiers, and crash data.

3.6 Tracking Data and Cookies

We use "Cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help us analyze how users use our services, and similar technologies (e.g. web beacons, pixels, ad tags and device identifiers) to recognize you and/or your device(s) on, off and across different devices and our services, as well as to improve the services we are offering, to improve marketing, analytics or website functionality. The use of Cookies is standard on the internet. Although most web browsers automatically accept cookies, the decision of whether to accept or not is yours. You may adjust your browser settings to prevent the reception of cookies, or to provide notification whenever a cookie is sent to you. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to access the full functionality of our websites.When you visit any of our services, our servers log your global IP address, which is a number that is automatically assigned to the network your computer is part of.

3.7 Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on visitors' computers, to help the website operators analyze how visitors use the site. The information generated by the cookie about the visitors' use of the website will generally be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States.On this website, IP anonymization has been activated. The IP addresses users visiting Cherry Credits websites will be shortened. Only in exceptional cases will a complete IP address be transferred to a Google server in the United States and shortened there. On behalf of the website operator, Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating the website for its users, in order to compile reports on website activity, and to provide other services relating to website activity and internet usage for website operators.Google will not associate the IP address transferred in the context of Google Analytics with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that in this case you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.Furthermore, users can prevent the collection of data about their use of the website (including their IP address) generated by the cookie, and the processing of data by Google, by downloading and installing the browser plug-in through the following link: [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

3.8 Content Recommendations

We may process information collected under this section 3 so that content, products and services shown on the pages of the Cherry Credits websites can be tailored to meet your needs and populated with relevant recommendations and offers. This is done to improve your customer experience. Subject to your separate consent or where explicitly permitted under applicable laws on email marketing, Cherry Credits may send you marketing messages about products and services offered by Cherry Credits to your email address and/or mobile number. In such a case we may also use your collected information to customise such marketing messages as well as collect information on whether you opened such messages and which links in their text you followed. You can opt out or withdraw your consent to receive marketing emails / text messages at any time by either withdrawing the consent on the “Manage Account” page or clicking the "unsubscribe" link provided in every marketing email.

We may at times, need to send your information to companies who work on behalf of Cherry Credits to provide a product or service to you. (Unless explicitly specified, these companies DO NOT have any rights to use any information we provide to them beyond what is necessary)

3.9 Data Required to Detect Violations

We collect certain data that is required for our detection, investigation and prevention of fraud, cheating and other violations of the Terms and Conditions, End User Licensing Agreement, Game Abuse Policy and applicable laws ("Violations"). This data is used only for the purposes of detection, investigation, prevention and, where applicable, acting on of such Violations and stored only for the minimum amount of time needed for this purpose. If the data indicates that a Violation has occurred, we will further store the data for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims during the applicable statute of limitations or until a legal case related to it has been resolved. Please note that the specific data stored for this purpose may not be disclosed to you if the disclosure will compromise the mechanism through which we detect, investigate and prevent such Violations.

We may use these data to respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process.

### 4\. How long we store your data

We will only store your information as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes for which the information is collected and processed or — where the applicable law provides for longer storage and retention period — for the storage and retention period required by law. After that your Personal Data will be deleted, blocked or anonymized, as provided by applicable law.

In particular: 

  * If you terminate your Cherry account, your Personal Data will be marked for deletion except to the degree legal requirements or other prevailing legitimate purposes dictate a longer storage.
  * In certain cases, Personal Data cannot be completely deleted in order to ensure the consistency of the gameplay experience. For instance, matches you have played that affect other players' matchmaking data and scores will not be deleted; rather, your connection to these matches will be permanently anonymized.
  * Please note that Cherry Credits is required under The Companies Act of Singapore to keep records of transactions connected with our business and services for a period of at least five (05) years.
  * If you withdraw your consent on which a processing of your Personal Data or of the Personal Data of your child is based, we will delete your Personal Data respectively the Personal Data of your child without undue delay to the extent that the collection and processing of the Personal Data was based on the withdrawn consent.
  * If you exercise a right to object to the processing of your Personal Data, we will review your objection and delete your Personal Data that we processed for the purpose to which you objected without undue delay, unless another legal basis for processing and retaining this data exists or unless applicable law requires us to retain the data.

### 5\. Who has access to your data

5.1 Cherry Credits may use your Personal Data to the degree necessary to achieve the purposes listed in section 2 and 3 above. In the event of a reorganization, sale or merger we may transfer Personal Data to the relevant third party subject to applicable laws.

5.2 We may also share your Personal Data with our third party providers that provide customer support services in connection with goods, Content and Services distributed via Cherry Credits. Your Personal Data will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy and only as far as this is necessary for performing customer support services. 

5.3 In accordance with internet standards, we may also share certain information (including your IP address) with our third party network providers that provide content delivery network services and game server services in connection with Cherry Credits. Our content delivery network providers enable the delivery of digital content you have requested, e.g. when using Cherry Game Clients, by using a system of distributed servers that deliver the content to you, based on your geographic location.

5.4 The Cherry community includes forums, where users can exchange ideas and communicate with each other. When posting a message to the forum, please be aware that the information is being made publicly available online; therefore, you are doing so at your own risk. If your Personal Data is posted on one of our community forums against your will, please contat us via Cherry Messenger to request its removal.

5.5 Cherry Credits may release Personal Data to comply with court orders or laws and regulations that require us to disclose such information.

### 6\. How we protect your personal information

We take great precautions to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

We use Transport Layer Security (TLS) 1.2 encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. In order to make any purchase, you must use an TLS-enabled browser such as Microsoft Edge, Firefox or Chrome etc. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal and payment information while it's transmitted over the Internet.

You can also help us by taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords regularly and make sure you use a secure web browser. In addition, never reveal to any one your 6-digit security PIN and secret question / answer.

### 7\. Integrity of your personal information

It is very important to ensure that all submitted personal information during registration is accurate, complete, and up to date for the purposes for which it is used. Please note that while you have the right to access, correct and update personal information, certain information is non-changeable upon submission for security reasons. Do ensure that your contact information and preferences are up-to-date by updating your Cherry account whenever necessary.

Your email address provided may be used to inform you of our latest news and announcements. You may opt out of this by unchecking the newsletter box during registration, via the Manage Account function or choosing to unsubscribe from our mailing list.

### 8\. How can you verify, modify or delete your personal information

You may verify and modify your Personal Data that we hold about you by logging into your Cherry account, or contacting our customer support via Cherry Messenger.

If we process your Personal Data, we shall endeavor to ensure by implementing suitable measures that your Personal Data is accurate and up-to-date for the purposes for which it was collected. If your Personal Data is inaccurate or incomplete, you can change the information you provided via the above two means.

You may request the deletion of Personal Data concerning you if the reason why we could collect it (see section 2 and 3 above) does not exist anymore or if there is another legal ground for its deletion. For individual items of Personal Data please edit them through your Cherry account or request the deletion via our customer support using Cherry Messenger. You are required to provide your personal identity information for the deletion request to verify that you are the genuine owner of the Cherry account.

As a result of deleting your Cherry account, you will lose access to all Cherry Credits services, including your Cherry account, e-wallet, Cherry Game accounts, game-related information linked to the Cherry account and the possibility to access other services you are using the Cherry account for.

We allow you to restore your Cherry account with a grace period of 30 (thirty) calendar days from the moment you request deletion of your Cherry account. This functionality allows you not to lose your account by mistake, because of your loss of your account credentials or due to hacking. During the suspension period, we will be able to finalize financial and other activities that you may have initiated before sending the Cherry account deletion request. After the grace period, Personal Data associated with your account will be deleted subject to section 4. above

In some cases, deletion of your Cherry account, and therefore Personal Data deletion, is complicated. Namely, if your account has a business relationship with Cherry Credits, such as due to your work for Cherry Credits or a game developer, you will only be able to delete your Cherry account after you have transferred this role to another user or have dissolved the business relationship. In some cases, considering the complexity and number of the requests, the period for Personal Data erasure may be extended, but for no longer than three further months.

### 9\. Links to Third Party Sites

Our website may contain links to or references to other websites that may be accessed or which may originate outside the boundaries of our websites and which information we will have no control. Cherry Credits shall have no obligation or responsibility regarding any content derived, obtained, accessed within through or outside of our websites. Any inclusion of links to such external website does not imply any endorsement or verification of the material on such website or any association with their operators, and such website shall be accessed at your own risk.

### 10\. Contact Info

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or your personal data, please contact us via Cherry Messenger. Alternatively, you may email us at [dpo@cherrycredits.com](mailto:dpo@cherrycredits.com).

3 Fusionopolis Way Symbiosis #11-27   
Singapore 138633   
Office Contact: 6747 6676   
Customer Service Contact: [gardener at cherrycredits dot com](mailto:gardener@cherrycredits.com)

### 11\. Revisions to the Privacy Policy

We may change or update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review the latest version of our Privacy Policy posted on this webpage. The changes that are posted shall take effect immediately. Please contact us at [dpo@cherrycredits.com](mailto:dpo@cherrycredits.com) if you no longer wish for us to collect, use or disclose your personal identifiable information
